American Hardware Corporation Records
© 2003 University of Connecticut
- Series V: P. & F. Corbin, 1859-1944
  - Office payroll, 1908 (Box 460)
  - Office payroll, 1909 (Box 461)
  - Office payroll, 1910 (Box 462)
  - Office payroll, 1911 (Box 463)
  - Office payroll, 1912 (Box 464)
  - Office payroll, 1913 (Box 465)
  - Office payroll, 1914 (Box 466)
  - Office payroll, 1915 (Box 467)
  - Office payroll, 1916 (Box 468)
  - Office payroll, 1917 (Box 469)
  - Office payroll, 1918 (Box 470)
  - Office payroll, 1919 (Box 471)
  - Office payroll, 1920 (Box 472)
  - Office payroll, 1921 (Box 473)
  - Office payroll, 1922 (Box 474)
  - Office payroll, 1923 (Box 475)
  - Office payroll, 1924 (Box 476)
  - Office payroll, 1925 (Box 477)
  - Office payroll, 1926 (Box 478)
  - Office payroll, 1927 (Box 479)
  - Office payroll, 1928 (Box 480)
  - Office payroll, 1929-1934 (Box 481)
  - Office payroll, Philadelphia and New York, 1920 (Box 482)
  - Office payroll, Philadelphia and New York, 1921 (Box 483)
  - Office payroll, Philadelphia and New York, 1922 (Box 484)
  - Office payroll, Philadelphia and New York, 1923 (Box 485)
  - Office payroll, Philadelphia and New York, 1925 (Box 486)
  - Office payroll, Philadelphia and New York, 1926 (Box 487)
  - Office payroll, Philadelphia and New York, 1927 (Box 488)
  - Office payroll, Philadelphia and New York, 1928 (Box 489)
  - General index, 1915 (Box 490)
  - General ledger index, 1918-1920 (Box 491)
  - Cashbook, 1859-1863 (Box 492)
  - Cashbook, 1864-1865 (Box 493)
  - Cash accounts, 1866-1870 (Box 494)
  - Cashbook, 1876-1878 (Box 495)
  - General cash (with labor information), 1877 (Box 496)
  - Cashbook, 1895 (Box 497)
  - Cashbook, 1900 (Box 498)
  - Cash, 1903 (Box 499)
  - Cashbook, 1907 (Box 500)
  - Cashbook, 1908 (Box 501)
  - Cashbook, 1911 (Box 502)
  - Cashbook, 1913 (Box 503)
  - Cashbook, 1915 (Box 504)
  - Cashbook, 1917 (Box 505)
  - Cashbook, 1919 (Box 506)
  - Cashbook, 1920 (Box 507)
  - Cash, 1930-1933 (Box 508)
  - Cashbook, 1932 (Box 509)
  - Cashbook, 1934 (Box 510)
  - Purchase ledger, 1892 (Box 513)
  - Purchase ledger, 1899 (Box 514)
  - Purchase ledger, 1901 (Box 515)
  - Purchase ledger, 1912 (Box 516)
  - Purchase ledger, 1914 (Box 517)
  - Purchase ledger, 1916 (Box 518)
  - Purchase voucher register, 1921-1922 (Box 519)
  - Purchase voucher register, 1924 (Box 520)
  - Purchase voucher register, 1925 (Box 521)
  - Purchase voucher register, 1925 (Box 522)
  - Expense book of company executives, undated (Box 523)
  - Credit journal, 1911-1913 (Box 524)
  - Credit journal, 1914 (Box 525)
  - Credit journal, 1915 (Box 526)
  - Credit journal, 1917-1919 (Box 527)
  - Credit journal, 1928-1929 (Box 528)
  - Credit journal, 1929-1930 (Box 529)
  - Purchase voucher register, 1932-1933 (Box 530)
  - Payables, 1930-1935 (Box 531)
  - Accounts payable, 1932 (Box 532)
  - Accounts payable, 1935 (Box 533)
  - List of employees who purchased liberty bonds, 1917 (Box 534:1)
  - Trial/balance, 1908-1910 (Box 536)
  - Trial/balance (stock), 1921-1925 (Box 537)
  - Trial/balance, 1925-1932 (Box 538)
  - Sales book no. 5, 1866-1868 (Box 539)
  - Sales book, 1868-1869 (Box 540)
  - Sales book, 1869-1870 (Box 541)
  - Sales book, 1874 (Box 542)
  - Daybook and journal, 1862-1865 (Box 543)
  - Daybook and journal no. 8, 1872-1874 (Box 544)
  - Daybook and journal, 1874-1876 (Box 545)
  - Daybook and journal, 1877-1878 (Box 546)
  - Daybook and journal, 1881-1886 (Box 547)
  - Daybook and journal, 1862-1865 (Box 548)
  - Notes receivable, 1913 (Box 549)
  - Notes receivable, 1921 (Box 550)
  - Notes receivable, 1927-1931 (Box 551)
  - Ledger, 1859-1865 (Box 552)
  - Ledger, 1866-1871 (Box 553)
  - Ledger, 1885-1887 (Box 554)
  - General ledger, 1914 (Box 555)
  - General ledger, 1915 (Box 556)
  - General ledger, 1916 (Box 557)
  - General ledger, 1917 (Box 558)
  - General ledger, 1918 (Box 559)
  - General ledger, 1919 (Box 560)
  - General ledger, 1920 (Box 561)
  - General ledger, 1925 (Box 562)
  - General ledger, 1931-1932 (Box 563)
  - Journal, 1896 (Box 564)
  - Journal, 1901 (Box 565)
  - Journal, 1908 (Box 566)
  - Journal, 1910 (Box 567)
  - Journal, 1918 (Box 568)
  - Journal, 1918-1927 (Box 569)
  - Petty cash, 1867-1869 (Box 511)
  - Petty cash, 1869-1871 (Box 512)
  - Petty cash, 1917-1919 (Box 570)
  - Private ledger, 1907 (Box 571)
  - Parcel post, 1936-1937 (Box 572)
  - U.S. War Savings Bonds register, 1942-1944 (Box 573)
  - Proof book, 1927-1934 (Box 574)